<Documentation>
  <Docs DocId="T:Foundation.NSInputStream">
    <summary>A read-only input NSStream.</summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        <format type="text/html">
          <h3>Subclassing NSInputStream.</h3>
        </format>
		
		NSInputStream is a concrete subclass of NSStream you can use to give read-only 
		access to stream data. For most cases this is sufficient, however if you want
		more control over the data, you can subclass NSInputStream. If you subclass NSInputStream
		you must provide an implementation of the following methods:
		<list type="bullet"><item><term><see cref="Foundation.NSInputStream.Read(IntPtr,uint)" />: In this
					method you must write bytes to the provided buffer. You can use
					<see cref="System.Runtime.InteropServices.Marshal.Copy(byte[],int,IntPtr,int)" />
					to write from a byte array to the provided buffer. Return the number of bytes
					actually written.
				</term></item><item><term><see cref="Foundation.NSInputStream.GetBuffer(ref System.IntPtr,ref System.UIntPtr)" />: Return
					a pointer to a buffer where bytes can be read. You can return false from this
					method and just implement <see cref="Foundation.NSInputStream.Read(IntPtr,uint)" />.
				</term></item><item><term><see cref="Foundation.NSInputStream.HasBytesAvailable" />: Use
					this method to indicate when your stream has data to be read.
				</term></item></list></para>
      <format type="text/html">
        <h3>Providing a toll-free bridged NSInputStream subclass.</h3>
      </format>
      <para>
        <format type="text/html">
          <b>The methods required to provide a toll-free bridged NSInputStream subclass are considered private API,
			and may cause Apple to reject your app from the App Store.</b>
        </format>
      </para>
      <para>
		An simple NSInputStream subclass will not work for all API that takes an NSInputStream.
		This is the case with <see cref="Foundation.NSMutableUrlRequest" /> for
		instance, which actually expects an instance of a CFReadStream object. For this to work
		our NSInputStream subclass needs to be toll-free bridged to CFReadStream. This is
		done by overriding the following methods:
		<list type="bullet"><item><term><see cref="Foundation.NSInputStream.SetCFClientFlags(CoreFoundation.CFStreamEventType,System.IntPtr,System.IntPtr)" />: 
					This method is called to register a client to notify of events in your
					stream. You must call the base implementation, with the exact arguments passed
					in.
				</term></item><item><term><see cref="Foundation.NSInputStream.ScheduleInCFRunLoop(IntPtr,string)" />:
					Depending on what you're doing to provide the data, you will need to schedule
					in a run loop when this method is called. You should not call the base
					implementation for this method.
				</term></item><item><term><see cref="Foundation.NSInputStream.UnscheduleInCFRunLoop(IntPtr,string)" />:
					This is called when you need to unschedule from a run loop. You should not call
					the base implementation for this method.
				</term></item></list>
		You must call also <see cref="Foundation.NSInputStream.Notify((valuetype CoreFoundation.CFStreamEventType)" />
		to inform the client when you have data available (or when you have any other relevant
		event), otherwise your input stream won't be read from.
	</para>
    </remarks>
    <related type="externalDocumentation" href="https://developer.apple.com/library/ios/documentation/Cocoa/Reference/Foundation/Classes/NSInputStream_Class/index.html">Apple documentation for <c>NSInputStream</c></related>
  </Docs>
  <Docs DocId="M:Foundation.NSInputStream.Dispose(System.Boolean)">
        <param name="disposing">
          <para>If set to <see langword="true" />, the method is invoked directly and will dispose managed and unmanaged resources;   If set to <see langword="false" /> the method is being called by the garbage collector finalizer and should only release unmanaged resources.</para>
        </param>
        <summary>Releases the resources used by the NSInputStream object.</summary>
        <remarks>
          <para>This Dispose method releases the resources used by the NSInputStream class.</para>
          <para>This method is called by both the Dispose() method and the object finalizer (Finalize).    When invoked by the Dispose method, the parameter disposing <paramref name="disposing" /> is set to <see langword="true" /> and any managed object references that this object holds are also disposed or released;  when invoked by the object finalizer, on the finalizer thread the value is set to <see langword="false" />. </para>
          <para>Calling the Dispose method when the application is finished using the NSInputStream ensures that all external resources used by this managed object are released as soon as possible.  Once developers have invoked the Dispose method, the object is no longer useful and developers should no longer make any calls to it.</para>
          <para>  For more information on how to override this method and on the Dispose/IDisposable pattern, read the ``Implementing a Dispose Method'' document at https://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/fs2xkftw.aspx</para>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
</Documentation>