<Documentation>
  <Docs DocId="T:CoreFoundation.DispatchObject">
    <summary>Base class for dispatch objects.</summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
	Dispatch objects share functions for coordinating memory management, suspension, cancellation and con-
	text pointers. While all dispatch objects are retainable, not all objects support suspension, context
	pointers or finalizers (currently only queues and sources support these additional interfaces).
      </para>
      <para>
	The invocation of blocks on dispatch queues or dispatch sources may be suspended or resumed with the
	methods <see cref="CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.Suspend()" /> and <see cref="CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.Resume()" /> respectively. The dispatch framework always checks
	the suspension status before executing a block, but such changes never affect a block during execution
	(non-preemptive).  Therefore the suspension of an object is asynchronous, unless it is performed from
	the context of the target queue for the given object.  The result of suspending or resuming an object
	that is not a dispatch queue or a dispatch source is undefined.

      </para>
      <para>
	Important: suspension applies to all aspects of the dispatch
	object life cycle, including the finalizer function and
	cancellation handler. Therefore it is important to balance
	calls to <see cref="CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.Suspend()" />
	and <see cref="CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.Resume()" />
	such that the dispatch object is fully resumed when the last
	reference is released.  The result of releasing all references
	to a dispatch object while in a suspended state is undefined.

      </para>
      <para>
	Dispatch queues and sources support supplemental context pointers. The value of the context point may
	be retrieved and updated with the <see cref="CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.Context" /> property.

      </para>
      <para>
	The result of getting or setting the context of an object that is not a dispatch queue or a dispatch
	source is undefined.	

      </para>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Documentation>