<Documentation>
  <Docs DocId="M:CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.#ctor(System.String,System.Boolean)">
    <param name="label">Name for the dispatch queue, as a convention, use reverse-style DNS names for your queue name.</param>
    <param name="concurrent">If set, the dispatch queue can invoke the submitted blocks concurrently.</param>
    <summary>Creates a named dispatch queue that can optionally
	execute any submitted code concurrently.</summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
	    If the <paramref name="concurrent" /> is set to <see langword="false" /> this is equivalent to calling the
	    constructor tht takes a single string argument.   That is,
	    it will execute all submitted code blocks serially, one
	    after another.
	  </para>
      <para>
	    If the value is <see langword="true" /> then the queue can
	    execute the code blocks concurrently.   In this mode, you
	    can use the <see cref="M:CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.DispatchBarrierAsync(System.Action)" />
	    method to submit a code block that will wait for all
	    pending concurrent blocks to complete execution, then it
	    will execute the code block to completion.   During the
	    time that the barrier executes, any other code blocks
	    submitted are queued, and will be scheduled to run
	    (possibly concurrently) after the barrier method completes.
	  </para>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
  <Docs DocId="T:CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue">
    <summary>Provides a task queue that can perform tasks either synchronously or asynchronously.</summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
	Queues are the fundamental mechanism for scheduling blocks for
	execution within the Apple Grand Central Dispatch framework.
      </para>
      <para> All blocks submitted to dispatch queues are dequeued in
	FIFO order.  By default, queues created with the default
	constructor wait for the previously dequeued block to complete
	before dequeuing the next block. This FIFO completion behavior
	is sometimes simply described as a "serial queue."  Queues are
	not bound to any specific thread of execution and blocks
	submitted to independent queues may execute concurrently.
	Queues, like all dispatch objects, are reference counted and
	newly created queues have a reference count of one.
      </para>
      <para>
	Concurrent dispatch queues are created by passing <see langword="true" /> as the value for the concurrent parameter on
	the constructor.  Concurrent queues may invoke blocks
	concurrently (similarly to the global concurrent queues, but
	potentially with more overhead), and support barrier blocks
	submitted with the dispatch barrier API, which e.g. enables
	the implementation of efficient reader-writer schemes.

      </para>
      <para>
	The optional label argument is used to describe the purpose of
	the queue and is useful during debugging and performance
	analysis. By convention, clients should pass a reverse DNS
	style label.  If a label is provided, it is copied. If a label
	is not provided, then Label property returns an empty C
	string.  For example:

      </para>
      <example>
        <code lang="csharp lang-csharp"><![CDATA[
	  var my_queue = new DispatchQueue ("com.example.subsystem.taskXYZ");
	]]></code>
      </example>
      <para>
	Queues may be temporarily suspended and resumed with the
	functions <see cref="M:CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.Suspend" />
	and <see cref="M:CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.Resume" />
	respectively. Suspension is checked prior to block execution
	and is not preemptive.

      </para>
      <para>
	Dispatch queue is <format type="text/html"><a href="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/search/index?search=System%20Threading%20Synchronization%20Context&amp;scope=Xamarin" title="T:System.Threading.SynchronizationContext">T:System.Threading.SynchronizationContext</a></format> aware and unless there is
	custom synchronization context set for the thread it will install its own synchronization context to
	ensure any context dispatch ends up on same dispatch queue.
      </para>
      <format type="text/html">
        <h2>Dispatch Barrier API</h2>
      </format>
      <para>
	The dispatch barrier API is a mechanism for submitting barrier blocks to a
	dispatch queue, analogous to the <see cref="M:CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.DispatchAsync(System.Action)" />/<see cref="M:CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.DispatchSync(System.Action)" />
	methods.
	It enables the implementation of efficient reader/writer schemes.
	Barrier blocks only behave specially when submitted to
	concurrent queues ; on such a queue, a barrier block
	will not run until all blocks submitted to the queue earlier have completed,
	and any blocks submitted to the queue after a barrier block will not run
	until the barrier block has completed.
	When submitted to a a global queue or to a non-concurrent queue, barrier blocks behave identically to
	blocks submitted with the <see cref="M:CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.DispatchAsync(System.Action)" />/<see cref="M:CoreFoundation.DispatchQueue.DispatchSync(System.Action)" /> methods.
      </para>
    </remarks>
    <related type="sample" href="https://github.com/xamarin/ios-samples/tree/master/AVCaptureFrames/">avcaptureframes</related>
    <related type="sample" href="https://github.com/xamarin/ios-samples/tree/master/CoreTelephonyDemo/">CoreTelephonyDemo</related>
  </Docs>
</Documentation>